A Guide to the Christian de Duve papers, Rockefeller University Faculty, Accession 2009:084 FA934
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Dissertation, "La Lactoferrine Proteine des Secretions Externes et des Leucocytes Neutrophiles", Pierre Masson (Box 73)
- Dissertation, "Caractéristiques et Propiétés Antigéniques des Lysosomes du Foie", André Trouet, 1969 (Box 73)
- Dissertation, "La Lactoferrine Proteine des Secretions Externes et des Leucocytes Neutrophiles", Pierre Masson (Box 73)
- Dissertation, "Caractéristiques et Propiétés Antigéniques des Lysosomes du Foie", André Trouet, 1969 (Box 73)
- DIssertation, "Les Mucopolysaccharidoses en tant que Thesaurismoses Lysosomiales": François Van Hoof, 1972 (Box 73)
- Dissertation, "Etude Experimentale de la Surcharge des Lysosomes", Robert Wattiaux, 1966 (Box 74)
- Publication, "The Lysosome Concept", Christian de Duve, Lysosomes- CIBA Foundation Symposium, 1963 (Box 74)
- Publication, "Bolus Application of a Novel Recombinant Plasminogen Activator in Acute Myocardial Infarction Patients-Pharmacokinetics and Effects on the Hemostatic System", E. Seifried, M.M. Müller, U. Martin, et al., Plasminogen Activation in Gibrinolysis, in Tissue Remodeling, and in Development: Annals of the New York Academy of Sciences, Vol. 667, 1992 (Box 74)
- Publication, Current Aspects of Biochemical Energetics, Fritz Lipmann Dedicatory Volume, 1966 (Box 74)
- Publication, "Chapter 1, General Principles" in Enzyme Cytology, Christian de Duve, 1967 (Box 74)
- Publication, Ludwig Institute for Cancer Research, Annual Scientific Report, 1989 (Box 74)
- Publication, Waldzell Meeting, 2004 (Box 74)
- Publication, Louvain-en-Woluwe, de Bont and Van de Kerckhove, 1980 (Box 74)
- Publication, L'Oréal for Women in Science, 2002 (Box 74)
- Publication, Rockefeller University Directory of Graduates, 2000-2001 (Box 74)
- Publication, Inside the Cell-The New Frontier in Medical Science", Series- A New Medical Science for the 21st Century, Maya Pines, 1978 (Box 74)
- Publication, Annual Report, The Extramural Program of Research on Aging of the National Institute of Child Health and Human Development, Fiscal Year 1973 (Box 74)
- Publication, Rockefeller University (RU), Annual Reports, 1968-1968 (Box 74)
- Publication, Rockefeller University (RU), Scientific and Educational Programs, 1983-1989 (Box 74)
- Publication, Rockefeller University (RU), Directories, 1985-1989 (Box 74)
- Publication, Miscellaneous Rockefeller University (RU) Publications, 1960-1968, 19680 (Box 75)
- Publication, "Treinta Años de Investigación en Bioenergética", Manuel Losada Villasante, 1987 (Box 75)
- Publication, Blueprint for a Cell, The Nature and Origin of Life, Christian de Duve, 1991 (Box 75)
- Publication, A Guided Tour of the Living Cell, Vol. 1 and 2, Christian de Duve, 1984 (Box 75)
- Publication, Life Evolving-Molecules, Mind and Meaning, Christian de Duve, 2002 (Box 75)
- Publication, Vital Dust, Life as Cosmic Imperative, Christian de Duve, 1995 (Box 75)
- Reprint, "Translocation of Acyl-CoA Oxidase into Peroxisomes Requires ATP Hydrolysis but Not a Membrane Potential", Tsuneo Imanaka, Gillian M. Small, and Paul B. Lazarow, 1987 (Box 76)
- Reprint, "Biogenesis of the Glycosome in Trypanosoma brucei, The Synthesis, Translocation, and Turnover of Glycosomal Polypeptides", David T. Hart, Pierre Baudhuin, Fred R. Opperdoes, and Christian de Duve, 1987 (Box 76)
- Reprint, "Calcium Antagonism and Calcium Entry Blockade", Theophile Godfraind, Robert Miller, and Maurice Wibo, 1986 (Box 76)
- Reprint, "Real Brains and Artificial Intelligence", George N. Reeke, Jr. and Gerald M. Edelman, 1987 (Box 76)
- Reprint, "Most Proteins, Including Fructose Bisphosphate Aldolase, Are Stable in the Procyclic Trypomastigote Form of Trypanosoma brucei", Christine E. Clayton (Box 76)
- Reprint, "Albert Claude and the Beginnings of Biological Electron, Microscopy", George E. Palade (Box 76)
- Reprint, "Tissue Fractionation Past and Present", Christian de Duve, 1971 (Box 76)
- RUnion, Directory of Graduates, 1959-1984 (Box 76)